well anyway how are you how are you how is
bueno en fin cómo estáis cómo estáis
the acne it's me
como también el acné
remember to upload it to members please to
yo soy yo recuerda subirlo a miembros
help me in my new job
porfa que me ayudan en mi nuevo trabajo
serene health is javi there's no need
de sereno salud es javi no hace falta
for humans to appear like
que los humanos deben aparecer como
see us the first person who donated and
vernos la primera persona que le donó y
merry christmas merry christmas too and
feliz navidad feliz navidad igualmente y
see thank you very much I'm glad you
ve muchísimas gracias me alegra que
lost your virginity with me
pierdas la virginidad conmigo ya no
this piece is no longer monetized okay thanks for the
monetizó este trozo vale gracias por la
promo of the novel javier is love today thank
promo de la novela javier es amor hoy
goodness I didn't remember it I came it's good thing I
menos mal que no la recordaba vine está
remembered my weapon
menos mal que me la recordaba mi arma
the bracelet of the last offspring that I
el brazalete del último vástago que lo
have it here okay I have it here to
tengo aquí vale que lo tengo aquí para
promote it and now I forget because
promocionarlo y ya se me olvida porque
I'm in a million things we're already
estoy en un millón de cosas ya estamos
in December a million things separate us
en diciembre nos separa un millón de
the bracelet from the last offspring I have
cosas el brazalete del último vástago yo
n't read it yet because I didn't have
no lo he leído todavía porque no tenía
time Laura welcome welcome and
tiempo laura bienvenida bienvenida y
thank you very much I haven't had time
muchísimas gracias no he tenido tiempo
but other colleagues to whom you
pero otros colegas a los que se las
send them have told me that they are very good not
manda me han dicho que están muy bien no
that it's a little novel without a youthful style
que es una novelita sin en plan juvenil
and other roll handsome roll
y demás rollito rollito guapo rollito
twilight roll I can't imagine no things and I don't
crepúsculo no me imagino no cosas y no
know how to buy them you read it because it's very
sé comprarlos lo leéis que está muy
cheap my  weapon and I'll leave the link in the
baratito mi arma y os dejo el link en la
description and what you told me about the members, I
descripción y lo de los miembros que me
don't need to
habéis dicho no hace falta que yo lo
upload it, I mean it's supposed to automatically
suba o sea se supone que automáticamente
pay monthly, some will have cut it off because of the
paga al mes algunos habrá cortado por el
copy and that's not why it gives it to me but that's why I don't
cop y no por eso me da pero por eso no
want to put the music tivo because then
quiero poner la música tivo porque luego
the copy jumps it blocks but as soon
salta el copy se bloquea pero nada más
as you enter the channel javi the canijo
que entráis en el canal javi el canijo
on the cover at the beginning
en la portada al principio aparecen
videos for members appear and there you have all
vídeos para miembros y ahí tenéis todos
the live shows, the pouts always came out
los directos siempre salieron los morros
okay if anything can't be seen what you
vale si acaso alguno no se ve lo que
have is to cut the
tengas es cortarle la parte de la
song part and maybe that's why anyway
canción y a lo mejor por eso en fin
the thing is that he was telling us he was going to
la cosa es que nos iba contado iba a
put something together that if they attacked the
montar algo a que sí os atacaron la
lottery
lotería
there's some millionaire around here who's
hay algún millonario por aquí que me
going to give me a million lion
vaya a dar un millón de lion
some millionaire let's
algún millonario
see how it seems that nobody has touched
a ver que como que nos ha tocado a nadie
it turned
la tocara
off in case I'll tell you what
se apagó por si os cuento lo que me ha
happened to me I'll tell you what happened to me with
pasado yo cuento lo que me ha pasado de
the pedrea well I get the pedrea
la pedrea bueno a mí me toca la pedrea
the pedrea that or rather the pedrea is 20
la pedrea que o sea la pedrea son los 20
euros the 100
euros los 100
food almost in daddy
alimento casi en papito
but you know what happened to me
pero sabéis lo que me ha pasado
well sure viruses good or not
bueno seguro virus buenos o no
and well they are your father of 530 sticks
y bueno son a tu padre de 530 palitos
is moving turn 530 you can win
está moviendo gire 530 te puede tocar
but how much of this position I do
pero qué cantidad de este puesto que yo
not understand why buying it from
no entiendo por qué lo comprando a los
colleagues and they called me from the
compañeros y me llamaron del trabajo
old job where I worked hey you know we are
antiguo donde yo trabajábamos oye sabes
going to order the lottery do you
que vamos a encargar la lotería quieres
want a ticket of course
quiere un boleto
I checked the total I say is that
claro comprobé lo total que digo es que
now it's these people's turn they will become
ahora le toque a esta gente se harán
millionaires and I'm not worth it after
millonarios y yo no vale
all when I bought it when I went to
total que cuando lo compré cuando fui a
pick it up I said look you were you how
recoger lo dije fíjate tú fuiste tú qué
stupid it is yes or look you how stupid it is
tonto es si o fíjate tú qué tonto es
but he must have asked for another
sino que tiene que haberle pedido otros
21 for my mother that sometimes I
21 para mi madre que algunas veces lo
bought it half with my mother when I have not been
compraba media con mi madre cuando no he
able to buy it and my mother has told me
podido comprarlo y mi madre me ha dicho
let's buy it half or then I
vamos lo compramos media o luego yo le
should have bought another one for my mother
tenía que haber comprado otro a mi madre
and another my mother in white they
y otra mi suegra en blanco ellos me
would have cost me 20 euros more each and
hubiera costado 20 euros más cada uno y
today and if it is won imagine that it is time to
hoy día y si toca sea imagínate que toca
put well it is my turn and my
poner pues me toca a mí y le toca a mi
mother's turn and my turn  mother in law and everyone
madre y le toca a mi suegra y todos
happy and one weekend I had to be stupid to
contentos y un finde tuve que tontería
surf the web having spent 40 euros more having
por navegar haberme gastado 40 euros más
periods more worth total than
haber periodos más vale total que
what deal Ryan that's why I have to see
qué trato ryan por eso yo hay que ver
that it's not just my mother I don't know what good do
que no sólo a mi madre no sé qué bueno
n't spend anything because they ask for the
no se pase nada porque ellos piden el
number they always buy the same number
número siempre compran el mismo número
for the benefit of the number that the line I
por provecho del número que the line
think is the number in which
creo que es el número en el que se
the company was inaugurated don't pay too much
inauguró la empresa no me echéis mucha
attention to me but I think it's always the same
cuenta pero creo que es siempre el mismo
number okay Denny and welcome
número vale denny y bienvenido
thank you very much total that for 40
muchísimas gracias total que ya por 40
euros more I would have bought it for my
euros más se lo hubiera comprar a mi
missionary mother but oh well it's already
madre misionera pero bueno ya está
late they can't charge and since
ya es tarde no se pueden cargar y como
today she left my cell phone at home in the
hoy me dejó el móvil en casa por la
morning okay I blocked the video at 10 in
mañana vale trabe el vídeo a las 10 de
the morning that she is up all night
la mañana que está toda la noche
compiling everything that they take
despierto por ciento recopilando todo lo
out the video too and when I
que lo que sacan el vídeo demás y cuando
leave she took me to the street I went to pick up the
me voy me bajó a la calle fui por la
girl from school and so on and when I come back go
niña al colegio y demás y cuando vuelvo
salmo I had paid because the
vaya a salmo había pagado por sin
battery was dead and when I come back with the cell phone and
batería y cuando vuelvo con el móvil y
my partner had spoken to me and she says she
me había hablado mi compañera y me dice
sent me a photo and puts a
me mandó una foto y pone una captura de
screenshot that says this number has
pantalla que pone a este número le ha
won
tocado
the entire series 20 thousand euros and you
la serie completa 20 mil euros y te ha
won 100 euros and
tocado en el décimo 100 euros y
mills and daddy
mills y en papito
how cool I don't say [ __ ] it never wins me it
que guay no digo [__] no me toca nunca
's my [ __ ] life it's my turn now
es la [__] vida me toca ahora
well then 1,100 sticks and not only have I
bueno pues 1.100 palitos y no sólo he
bought my mother God knows [ __ ] it could have gone
comprado a mi madre sabe dios ya [__]
to my mother a thousand
hubiera podido tocar a mi madre mil
euros 1,100 turkeys total I
euros 1.100 pavitos total
say one they go to the distributions and we give it
digo una pasan a los repartos y le damos
to your mother we distribute it the three of us give it to
a tu madre lo repartimos los tres le
your mother we give it to my mother and
damos tu madre le damos a mi madre y ya
when you're there I realize that I haven't
cuando estás me doy cuenta que no me han
won a thousand euros they burn it all there are a
tocado mil euros lo queman todos son
hundred
cien
Jose Manuel welcome a hundred to Villa
jose manuel bienvenido cien para villa
always how good they are Jose Manuel
siempre qué buenos son jose manuel
thanks
gracia
here I take you Jose Manuel I'm going to remove the
aquí te llevo josé manuel voy a quitar
wiring because it sounds to me and it's my turn for
cablería porque suene me y me toca de
total support and distributing the money
apoyo total y repartiendo de los dineros
and it turns out that since I didn't understand it
y resulta ser que como no lo entendía
well since I am a boomerang there is
bien como soy boomerang
a boom he doesn't understand the lottery
hay un boom él no entiende de la lotería
is that with her well I don't understand I didn't
es que con ella pues no entiendo no
understand the lottery total that was not what
entendí la lotería total que no era lo
you  he's saying it was a thousand the series
que te está diciendo era mil la serie
and if in the tenth it's 100 for me and I
y si en el décimo sea para mí 100 y yo
had understood that I had won
había entendido como que me había tocado
two different things one of a thousand and the others
dos cosas diferentes uno de mil y otros
I had understood it as I say take
yo lo había entendido como digo toma
won a thousand with the number and with the
tocado mil con el número y con la serie
mother series all always previous I understood
madre todos siempre anterior entendí
well and 2007 but no no if in payment of
bien y 2007 pero no no si en pago de
good dad for a beer my weapon
bueno papá por una cervecita mi arma
sex
sexo
welcome welcome thank you very much
bienvenido bienvenidos muchísimas
hey how are we doing members
gracias oye cómo vamos de miembros el
uncle Tyler thank you very much as master of
tio tyler muchísimas gracias como amo de
member he boasts something now that you're going
miembro ostenta una cosa ahora que vais
to freak out about how shameless man but
a flipar de la poca vergüenza tío pero
how shameless there was a
de la poquísima vergüenza había un
moment a little moment
momento un momentito
host range send more send a message
[__] gama manda más manda un mensaje
from amazon that he's buying a lot of the
de amazon que está comprando mucho los
headphones made that I know that he had
auriculares hechos que yo sabe que le
liked a lot okay and that's why he
había gustado muchísimo vale y por eso
leaves them in the description because I know that
los deja en la descripción porque sé que
now that we are in kings and so on, so
ahora que estamos en reyes y demás pues
do the shopping okay you have the link of
hacer las compras vale tenéis el link de
the description that many people
la descripción que mucha gente me
ask me about these headphones I are
pregunta por estos auricular yo somos
copying turbo plans for something that I
copiar turbo planes para una cosa que le
copy from the turbo plan street he copied a
copio al turbo plan calle me copió un
video now we're not going to see a turbo video
vídeo ahora no vamos a ver vídeo turbo
the total that while I  copied the video
la total que mientras me copió el vídeo
literally it is literally copied
literal es literal copiada
[Music]
[Música]
1,336 let's see if we get to 1,400
1.336 a ver si llegamos ya los 1.400
more miles so they can give me the nicknames I
millas más para que me den los de mote
take
que cojo
and I don't know what kid I've seen from ibai
y no sé qué cría habré visto yo de ibai
these days okay some click let's
en estos días vale algún click hayamos
put device these days that they come out
puesto device en estos días que me salen
recommended this channel okay
recomendado este canal vale clips
viral clips your fat [ __ ] okay and here
virales tu [__] gorda vale y el aquí
with his banner his icon as if
con su banner su icono como si fuera muy
the channel were very official okay look at the [ __ ]
oficial el canal vale mirar las [__]
visits
visitas
70,000 I mean
70.000 o sea
look thank you very much welcome I mean with
mira muchas gracias bienvenido o sea con
18 thousand subscribers
18 mil suscriptores
with 18 thousand subscribers look at the
con 18 mil suscriptores fijaros las
visits of three that
visitas de tres que se la ha posicionado
the videos have been positioned very well and of course how you
muy bien los vídeos y claro cómo vas
upload videos that are the same theme
subiendo vídeos que es la misma temática
okay well they keep coming out I
vale pues siguen saliendo les
recommended the people who see it and look at it
recomendaba la gente que lo ve y mira
70,000 the video that uploaded almost 24
70.000 el vídeo que subió hace casi 24
hours ago 144 thousand the day before 540 thousand
horas 144 mil el día anterior 540 mil
visits
visitas
the previous 210 thousand 273 thousand 488 thousand one hundred thousand one hundred thousand
el anterior 210 mil 273 mil 488 mil
300 thousand that is some
cien mil cien mil 300 mil o sea unas
incredible visits let's see the
visitas increíbles vamos a ver el
sociable
sociable
let's see the social point Blake if you
vamos a ver el punto social blake si os
notice every day he uploads the live shows
fijáis todos los días sube los directos
device the part that he likes the most about
device la parte que a él más le gusta de
ibai's live shows, I mean as if it were
los directos de ibai o sea como si fuera
me with my live shows on javier canijo
yo con mis directos en javier canijo
but being and vice but without being and vice
pero siendo y vice pero sin ser y vice
it's incredible not the little shame every
sea increíble no la poca vergüenza todos
day every day also it's not to
los días todos los días además no es
say that one day he uploads something from there and
decir que un día sube algo de ahí va y
that he liked it another day he uploads I don't know
que le ha gustado otro día sube no sé
what
qué
tell me my weapon without live shows let's
dime mi arma sin directo
see I'm live then I'll read you
a ver estoy directo luego te leo
my daughter my daughter the one with loves let's
mi hija mi hija la de amores
see the [ __ ] views
a ver las [__] visitas
damn fit
ostia fit
flip do the point channels I mean he had
flip haga el punto canales o sea tenía
eight thousand subscribers a week ago
ocho mil suscriptores hace una semana
a week okay of
una semana vale
course he deleted everything he had
claro ha eliminado todo lo que tuviera
before that week before this week he
antes de esa semana antes de esta semana
had something uploaded so with those who have
tenía algo subido con lo que con los que
reached eight thousand subscribers okay
ha llegado a ocho mil suscriptores vale
eight thousand subscribers he started uploading it
a ocho mil suscriptores empezó a subirlo
device flipa
device flipa
flipa I think there's a video with a
flipa lo creo que hay un vídeo con un
million there was a video with a million
millón había un vídeo con un millón
also it's always that almost all the
también siempre es que casi todos los
videos are 200 thousand and up and
vídeos son de 200 mil para arriba y la
most are 300 thousand half a million there was
mayoría son de 300 mil medio millón
one with a million  I would
había uno con un millón
swear
juraría
if this UAM, this Frank one costs a
si el uam este el de frank cuesta un
million and a half, Frank's one costs a
millón y medio el de frank cuesta un
million and a half, I mean, the guy, the guy used to
millón y medio o sea el tío el tío antes
upload something else, we don't know, the one who
subía otra cosa no sabemos el que que
reached eight thousand subscribers and suddenly,
llegó a ocho mil suscriptores y de
suddenly,
y de repente
no no no no no no no no no no no I was
no no no no no no no no no no me
wrong, I was wrong, I was wrong,
equivocado me equivocado me equivocado
8,000 subscribers, he didn't have a channel
a 8.000 suscriptores no tenía un canal
with 28 subscribers and 8 thousand views,
con 28 suscriptores y 8 mil visitas
the guy from Spain okay, well, look what he
el tío de españa vale pues mira lo que
does is that you're going to freak out, you're going to freak out,
hace es que vais a flipar vais a flipar
okay,
vale
I mean, 28 subscribers and 8 thousand views, he would
o sea 28 suscriptores y 8 mil visitas
have his best content okay, all of a
tendría lo mejor contenido suyo vale de
sudden he starts uploading videos,
repente empieza a subir los vídeos
device, and makes pop
device y hace pop
every day, gaining four thousand
todos los días ganando cuatro mil
subscribers and an average of two million
suscriptores y una media de dos millones
views, he's made 10 million views in a week,
de visitas ha hecho en una semana 10
okay,
vale
this doesn't stop here, the
esto no se queda aquí sino que coge el
guy goes today and uploads a video that he deleted
tío hoy y sube un vídeo que ha eliminado
because someone spoke to him on Instagram
porque ha hablado con él por instagram
okay, he uploads a video today at noon and
vale sube un vídeo hoy al mediodía y
puts the thumbnail, it was a
pone la miniatura era una pantalla
white screen with a phosphorescent letter, watching my
blanca con una letra fosforita viendo mi
channel,
canal
I'm like this, I
me quedo así
go into the video, he deleted it, I
me meto en el vídeo lo ha borrado me lo
should have downloaded it, dude, no  it
tenía que haber descargado tío no nos
fails us today in the video that I made of
falla hoy en el vídeo que he hecho de
living half of the things that I had to
vivir la mitad de cosas que tenía que
put have been screenshots because
poner han sido capturas porque han ido
they have been deleting things it always did not fail I sell my channel okay anyway I go to the video and I see it and the guy was bragging about statistics showing the youtube statistics and saying look 10 million views in the last seven days 18 thousand subscribers in the
siete días 18 mil suscriptores en los
last 10 days look at this channel pim pam
últimos 10 días mirar este canal pim pam
pum pam
pum pam
on top of bragging about statistics like
encima presumiendo de estadísticas como
the one who was selling you a marvel on
el que te estaba vendiendo una maravilla
top of that look at this
encima mirar esto
donations here donations at least
donaciones aquí donaciones por lo menos
here the guy has been smart because I
aquí el tío ha sido listo porque me he
got in right away what name does it show up in
metido de una vez que nombre me sale en
paypal and it doesn't show up his name I'm going to
el paypal y no sale su nombre voy a
find out who I am going to find out his
averiguar quién eje voy a averiguar su
identity about what he knows and let's see in the
identidad sobre lo sepa y a ver en los
videos you can also donate
vídeos también lo podrás
here you can donate here
puedes donar aquí se puede donar aquí
Iraq channel
canal de irak
and why the hell are we going to donate to you you
y por qué [__] te vamos a donar
can donate here and why I mean
puede donar aquí y por qué
also do you want me to give you
o sea también quieres que te regale
money
dinero
flip out flip out
flipa flipa
okay what happened he uploaded
vale qué es lo que ha pasado ha subido
the video is donate flip out upload the video
el vídeo es donar flipa a subir el vídeo
s selling his channel he must have
s vendiendo su canal me lo tiene que
downloaded it  because it was nice to see
haber descargado porque era lindo de ver
talking to me that's why I saw a screenshot of the
a hablarme por eso vi una captura del
twitter
twitter
moment go see it md
momento se vayan a verlo md
you stopped loving me when my
tú me dejaste de querer cuando más se me
homework would have been seen the most
hubieran visto los deberes
for some reason it was called
por algún motivo se llamaba
the browser a little let's see
el navegador un poco a ver
now look this is the screenshot I
ahora mira esta es la captura que yo
was
estaba
in a playlist
en una lista de reproducción que se
called aurum play reacting okay a
llamaba aurum play reaccionando vale una
playlist that had six
lista de reproducción que tenía seis
videos in private wine thank you
vídeos en privado vino muchísimas
very much thank you very much welcome okay that
muchísimas gracias bienvenido vale esa
playlist is no longer there either
lista de reproducción ya no está tampoco
greetings from chile my weapon I love you
saludos desde chile mi arma i love you
growing heart growing heart thank you thank you
corazón creciente corazón creciente
very much thank you very much
gracias gracias muchas gracias
that playlist deleted it or
esa lista de reproducción la borrado o
rather if I had that playlist it
sea si tenía esa lista de reproducción
means that before the device
quiere decir que antes de lo device
when I had 28 subscribers I tried
cuando tenía 28 suscriptores lo intento
uploading d auro
subiendo d auro
what happens is that from sauro the
lo que pasa que de sauro entre salta el
copy automatically jumps okay because I have to
copio automáticamente vale porque yo
try every day every time
tengo que tratar día cada vez que
d auro reacts to something telling him dude what
reacciona algo d auro diciéndole tío que
else to jump cop and take it away I don't know what he
más saltar cop y quitármelo no sé qué
knows how to be flipped out okay if you're interested
sabe ser flipa vale si estás interesado
in buying it contact me on instagram
en comprarlo contactame por instagram
viral clips or rather the guy's
clips virales o sea el tío en una semana
channel explodes with ibai content
le peta el canal con contenido de ibai
with ibai content
con contenido de ibai
and I was already thinking about selling it  he will have
y ya estaba pensando en venderlo
requested monetization they will not have
habrá pedido la monetización no se la
accepted it and he said at least
habrán aceptado y ha dicho por lo menos
in a [ __ ] week instead of taking
en una [__] semana sea en vez de [__] a
maybe now and saying oh well I'm going to be
lo mejor ahora y decir ah pues voy a ser
like the m of show I'm going to create my own
como el m de show voy a crear mi propio
content I delete the device and take advantage of
contenido borro lo device y aprovechó
these subscribers the video had
estos suscriptores el vídeo tenía en una
two thousand views in an hour or in other words the moment
hora dos mil visitas o sea en el momento
that we upload something device even if you
que nos sube algo device aunque lo
put it on the sachas at two thousand views
pongas en los sachas a dos mil visitas
in an hour
en una hora
touch it supports you touch your dick and the
tócate la apoya tócate la [__] y el
video is deleted because welcome the
vídeo la borrada porque bienvenido el
youtube avatar thank you very much the
avatar de youtube muchas gracias el
video is deleted because he speaks to him
vídeo la borrado porque le habla por
privately okay it will be auctioned and today I'm going to
privado vale licitará y hoy os voy a
tell you the conversation for you I'm going to
contar la conversación para los voy a
tell you the conversation this is illegal to
contar la conversación esto es ilegal
sell the channel it is illegal
vender canal es ilegal
you can report everyone yes but
podéis reportar todo el mundo sí pero
with the m of soles the field forced him yes
con el m de soles el campo lo obligó si
to the stories that you talk very quickly that
a los cuentos que habláis muy rápido que
writing people are telling him let
escribiendo gente le están diciendo deja
people do whatever they want you I
la gente que haga lo que quiera ustedes
'm an idiot you know that he will help with a
soy [__] sabe que ayudará con una
hand boy the editor of was going to thread to
mano chico el editor de iba a hilo a
contact has said what the [ __ ] is it uploading
contactar ha dicho que [__] está
remove it that's
subiendo quítalo
why he wants to sell it also
por eso lo quiere vender también
not only because he can't
no solamente porque no lo puede
monetize but because the editor of ibai
monetizar sino porque el editor de ibai
told him to go talk
le ha dicho que fuera
to talk because you have a mouth
habla a hablar porque tenéis boca
you talk because you have a mouth and you don't
habláis porque tenéis boca y no me
let me tell the thing man you
dejáis que cuente la cosa tío
don't know since I always know everything
no sabéis ya que yo siempre lo sé todo
the editor divine had seen this
el editor divine había visto esto ha
said this what the [ __ ] in a week the
dicho esto que [__] en una semana la
view look at the
vista
videos look at the clip
mira que hay videos mira que hay clip
total I tell him I say I'm going to pretend
total le digo digo voy a hacerme pasar
because I want to buy the channel and I
porque les quiero comprar el canal y les
talk to them I tell him I saw that he has
hablo le digo yo la he visto que tiene
a youtube account for sale and he says
una cuenta de youtube en venta y me dice
hello like that I tell him but he's monetizing and
hola así le digo pero está monetizando y
he says no and I tell him because they
me dice no y le digo porque te la han
rejected it because of the content you upload and he
rechazado por el contenido que sube y me
says no what did the editor diva tell me and
dice no que me ha dicho el editor diva y
please don't upload it
que por favor no lo suba
Harold welcome
harold bienvenido
thank you very much
muchas gracias
Leo without a filter controversial neo controversial
leo sin filtro polémico neo polémico
thank you very much and I tell him yes
muchas gracias y le digo es que sí
emanuel welcome welcome if it goes
emanuel bienvenido bienvenidos si se va
totally against the rules it goes
totalmente en contra las normas va
totally against the rules, that is, you
totalmente contra las normas o sea esto
have to report this so that youtube
lo tenéis que reportar para que youtube
closes them and I win it by ip so that
les cierre y lo gane por ip para que no
more channels cannot be created ok either because
se pueda crear más canales ok sea porque
this is totally illegal either  you're freaking out, you're
esto es totalmente ilegal sea flipas no
freaking out about what it's like to sell it,
flipa lo que está siendo encima venderlo
I'm freaking out about people, how little [ __ ]
yo flipo con la gente la poca [__]
shame they have, no, I was
vergüenza que tiene no a mí me ha hecho
amused by donations and it's like
gracia de donaciones y es como
donations because santi marn is that I
donaciones porque santi marín es que me
open a channel and I say the best
abro y un canal y digo los mejores
videos of aurum place and here a
vídeos de aurum place y por aquí un
banner of aurum play here the face of
banner de aurum play aquí la cara de
aurum play and I start to upload it the
aurum play y empiezo a subirlo los
best videos that seem to me
mejores vídeos que a mí me parezca
d'hebron play
d'hebron play
and donations donations for creating the
y donaciones donaciones por crearme el
channel and uploading the videos of the script
canal y subir los vídeos de los script
before
antes
and I tell him clearly the right is
y le digo yo a claro que la derecha está
for the content and I know
por el contenido y se no
what I was going there and he asked me not to upload it
que iba ahí me ha pedido que no lo suba
okay video don't upload the one that says click
vale vídeo que no subas el que dice clic
device and I tell him is that your channel if it
device y le digo es que tu canal si tan
rejects monetization to whoever you
rechaza la monetización al que se lo
sell it to high problem and he says well the
vendas elevada problema y dice bueno las
things you create your own content and I
cosas que crees tu propio contenido y le
tell him but he didn't have permission to upload it he
digo pero no tenía permiso de subirlo
is uploading this without
está subiendo esto sin el permiso de
ibai's permission and he says no longer
ibai y me dice no
that he doesn't have permission
ya no que no tenga permiso
the worst thing is to think that someone donated to him
lo peor es pensar que alguien le donó
man I don't think so
hombre no creo
well
bueno
go find out okay
vete a saber vale
and I tell him well how much does he want for it and he
y le digo bueno cuánto quiere por él y
tells me  the bidding is at 500 euros and
me dice la puja está en 500 euros y
ends today
acaba hoy
who's the [ __ ] this will
quién será el [__] esto será
probably be a lie being so that I can
mentira seguramente siendo para que yo
give him more he understands me and I say to him and
le dé más me entiende y le digo y por
why is he selling it he can't upload other videos
qué lo vende no puede subir otros vídeos
and he says because I want to focus on my
y me dice porque quiero centrarme en mi
work and I prefer that he take it again
trabajo y prefiero que lo lleve otra vez
if you want to get into your work
si quieres entrar te en tu trabajo
focus on your work and stop uploading
céntrate en tu trabajo y deja de subir
videos device
vídeos device
says I prefer that someone else take it
dice prefiero que lo lleve otra persona
since I'm not going to have time to
ya que yo no voy a tener tiempo para
make videos
hacer vídeos
literally to make videos
literales para hacer vídeos
I'm dying I'm
yo me muero
really dying I
yo me muero de verdad
stopped talking to him and after a while he
total le dejó de hablar y al rato me
says is he interested and after five
dice está interesado y a los cinco
minutes again two
minutos otra vez dos signos de
question marks and I say I have to
interrogación y le digo tengo que
think about it it smells strange to me and he says well I
pensármelo me huele raro y me dice pues
already have a buyer if he wants it he
ya tengo comprador si lo quiere me lo
has to tell me now God
tiene que decir ya dios
bless him well if you already bought it why are you
viva pues si ya tienes comprado para que
insisting
me estás insistiendo
why not only thanks to him and he says they are
porque no sólo gracias a él y me dice me
offering me 500 in case you want to upload it
ofrecen 500 por si quieres subirlo
and I say dude if you already have another
y le digo tío si ya tienes otro
buyer why do you insist
comprador para que me insiste
and I say it seems like a lot if you upload
y le digo me parece mucho si subes
videos that are not from ibai they don't even have
vídeos que no es de ibai no tienen ni
5,000 views  I can give you 100 euros
5.000 visitas yo te puedo dar 100 euros
let me know if you don't buy it and then he wouldn't
avísame si no te lo compra y ahí ya no
answer me you know but freak out with the [ __ ]
me contestaba sabe pero flipa con la
shameless
[__] poca vergüenza
freak out with the [ __ ] little thick chat
flipa con la [__] poca gruesa charlo
thank you so much queen of people I
muchísimas gracias reina de gentes
would be a member today thank you so much let's
estaría siendo miembro hoy muchísimas
see if we get to 1400 that
gracias a ver si llegamos a los 1400 que
I upload content that is mine I
yo subo contenido que es mío
bet on the account in private
apuesto a la cuenta en privada vídeo
daily video of the best clicks device the
diario de los mejores clics device los
best kilos castell support this is not
mejores kilitos castell apoya esto no es
a click
un clic
these are videos directly of 20
estos son vídeos directamente de 20
minutes of 15 minutes the best clicks
minutos de 15 minutos los mejores clics
how little shame how little
qué poca vergüenza que poquísimas
shame dude
vergüenza tío
really what
de verdad yo qué
for these things the youtubers put them
por estas cosas los youtubers ponerlos
of the content that a [ __ ] goal because
del contenido que un [__] golazo porque
then we have a
luego nosotros
great time with you but often I don't
lo paso genial contigo pero a menudo no
know who you're talking about crazy face face
sé de quién hablas cara de loco cara
smiling with superiority face
sonriendo con superioridad cara
smiling with sunglasses face
sonriendo con gafas de sol cara
smiling with horns you are not wrong
sonriendo con cuernos razón no te falta
in your arguments it is ugly to use
en tus argumentos está feo usar nombres
other people's names like that lollipop lollipop thanks
ajenos así piruleta piruleta gracias
Alejandro for the super chava I'm glad
alejandro por el súper chava alegro que
you have fun okay because
te diviertas vale
of these points
por culpa de estos puntos canales de
crappy channels the youtubers have to  walking around
[__] los youtubers tienen que andar
putting up content and that in the end
poniendo el contenido y eso al final nos
screws us over the channels that make reviews
jode a los canales que hacemos críticas
opinions polemics age because because
opiniones polémica edad porque porque
we make fair use and now
nosotros hacemos uso legítimo y ahora te
the [ __ ] thing is jumping on you it contains DEET
está saltando el puñetero contenga deet
okay and for example when the Taurus jumps on me
vale y yo por ejemplo cuando me salta el
in Playboy I tell him even though it
tauro en playboy le digo aunque me ha
jumped on me that I don't even talk to them about Pando the
saltado que ni les hablo de pando el
link and nobody takes it away from me thank you very much
link y me lo quita nadie muchísimas
but you could have written something
gracias pero podrías haber escrito algo
May taking advantage of the super chat
mayo aprovechando el súper chat
grace you know but if the
gracia sabes pero si me salta el
content of a Divx video jumps on me oh I don't
contenido de un vídeo divx ay yo no
know and vice I don't have contact with
conozco y vice no tengo contacto con
Ibai I
ibai
have to start fighting I lose the
me tengo que poner a pelar pierdo el
video for two weeks
vídeo durante dos semanas
touch your dick it
tócate la [__]
's a [ __ ] pain
es un [__] [__]
here Yolanda subscribe everyone here Yo
aca yolanda suscribiros todos acá yo
Land here I got the yang already why
landia acá yo le cayó el yang ya por qué
because Yolanda Daz and from work is going to
porque yolanda díaz y de trabajo va a
upload a video my brother already tremendous
subir un vídeo mi hermano ya tremenda
little shame May
poca vergüenza
thank you very much tremendous little
mayo muchísimas gracias tremenda poca
shame has tremendous little shame
vergüenza tiene tremenda poca vergüenza
reported these channels always report
reportado estos canales siempre reportar
stolen content and also is
contenidos robados y además está
trying to sell the channel okay it has
intentando vender el canal vale
been clumsy dude it's me clumsy because I
en sido torpe tío es yo torpe porque
should have put it in the
tenía que haber metido en el chat de
YouTube chat that  I'm going to do it later, it's going to
youtube que lo voy a hacer luego va a
end directly, I should have
terminar directo me tenía que haber
gone into the YouTube chat to tell him,
metido en el chat de youtube a decirle
hey, look, this guy is doing this and he
oye mira este está haciendo esto y
also deleted the video where he
además ha eliminado el vídeo donde
was selling the channel that is
estaba vendiendo el canal que lo está
selling it. Let's see that you're going to notice the
vendiendo vamos que vais a notar el
change of IP, okay,
cambio de ip vale
look, I know that they always delete
mira que sé que siempre borran las
things.
cositas